Claire Jacquet

front end web developer

PERSONAL INFORMATION

claire.j.jacquet@gmail.com

French, English bilingual
Spanish intermediary

Permis B

SKILLS

FRONT END

html css sass javascript
vue.js webpack - vue-cli 3
nuxt.js jquery node.js
bootstrap materializecss
wordpress cms git
reponsive design

WEB ANALYTICS

google analytics eurlerian

PROJECT MANAGEMENT TOOLS

github jira youtrack trello slack spark google g suite

DIGITAL CHANNELS

seo, management (integration, monitoring and optimization) of web campaigns (affiliation, social media, search, etc), reporting Intensive courses in web development & autodidactic projects helped me gain multiple skills in web development. I have a background in webmarketing following over 5 years of working & studying in various international environements.

Portfolio with my latest projects (2019): cookiesandwifi.ovh

EDUCATION & DIPLOMAS

CERTIFICATION OPQUAST

jan. 2018, Best practices Accessibilité / Qualité Web

CERTIFICATIONS TECHNIQUE D'INTEGRATION & DEVELOPEMENT WEB (CNCP)

oct - déc 2017, Webforce 3 - Lille

FORMATION INTENSIVE DÉVELOPPEUR WEB

mars - août 2017, Simplon.co - Roubaix

MASTER OF SCIENCE, DIGITAL MARKETING

2013 - 2014, UCD Smurfit Graduate Business School - Dublin

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

2005 - 2011, Utrecht University of Applied Sciences - The Netherlands

2005, Baccalauréat. Lycée Montébello de Lille

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

CHARGÉE DE CAMPAGNES WEBMARKETING - ANKAMA

2016, CDD of 5 months in Roubaix. Managed web campaigns (Dofus, Wakfu, mobile games etc) & technical projects

AD OPERATIONS SPECIALIST - TWITTER

2015, 2 months in San Francisco and Dublin

SOCIAL MEDIA WEBMARKETER - BFREE FOODS

2014, 3 months internship in Dublin

WEBMARKETER - SPLENDIA.COM

2009 - 2012, in Barcelona. Managed international web campaigns. Responsible for technical components & projects

MARKETING & SALES OPERATIONS, POWERSTORM

2007, 8 months internship in Amsterdam

Claire Jacquet

web developer | front end

INFORMATIONS PERSONNELLES

claire.j.jacquet@gmail.com

Français, Anglais bilingueEspagnol intermédaire

Permis B

COMPÉTENCES

FRONT END

html css sass javascript

vue.js webpack - vue-cli 3

nuxt.js jquery node.js

bootstrap materializecss

wordpress cms git

reponsive design

WEB ANALYTICS

google analytics eurlerian

OUTILS GESTION DE PROJETS

github jira youtrack trello

slack spark google g suite

DIGITAL CHANNELS

seo, gestion et intégration /
monitoring / optimisation de
campagnes web (affiliation, social
media, search, etc), reporting

Diverses formations intensives et projets en autodidacte m'ont permis d'acquérir différentes compétences dans le développement web suite à plus de 5 ans d'expérience en web-marketing dans divers environements internationaux.

Portfolio avec mes derniers projets (2019): cookiesandwifi.ovh

FORMATIONS & DIPLOMES

CERTIFICATION OPQUAST

jan. 2018, Best practices Accessibilité / Qualité Web

CERTIFICATIONS TECHNIQUE D'INTEGRATION & DEVELOPEMENT WEB (CNCP)

oct - déc 2017, Webforce 3 - Lille

FORMATION INTENSIVE DÉVELOPPEUR WEB

mars - août 2017, Simplon.co - Roubaix

MASTER OF SCIENCE, DIGITAL MARKETING

2013 - 2014, UCD Smurfit Graduate Business School - Dublin

BACHELOR OF BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

2005 - 2011, Utrecht University of Applied Sciences - The Netherlands

2005, Baccalauréat. Lycée Montébello de Lille

EXPÉRIENCES PROFESSIONNELLES

CHARGÉE DE CAMPAGNES WEBMARKETING - ANKAMA

2016, CDD de 5 mois à Roubaix. Gestion de campagnes web (Dofus, Wakfu, jeux mobiles etc) & projets techniques

AD OPERATIONS SPECIALIST - TWITTER

2015, 2 mois à San Francisco et Dublin

SOCIAL MEDIA WEBMARKETER - BFREE FOODS

2014, stage de 3 mois à Dublin

WEBMARKETER - SPLENDIA.COM

2009 - 2012, à Barcelone. Gestion de campagnes web internationales.Responsable de projets & intégrations techniques

MARKETING & SALES OPERATIONS, POWERSTORM

2007, stage 8 mois à Amsterdam